Guide to the Architectural Drawings and Maps of Yale University Buildings and Grounds
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Architectural drawings and maps (not microfilmed), Series II
  - 3:3 Garland Apartments (242 York St) (1 drawing), undated (Folder 334)
  - 3:7 University Theatre (222 York St) (28 drawings), undated (Folder 336)
  - 3:25 Pierson and Davenport Colleges
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 337)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 338)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 339)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 340)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 341)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 342)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 343)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 344)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 345)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 346)
    - originals (131 drawings), undated (Folder 347)
    - Pierson College squash court renovation (3 drawings), 1987 (Folder 832)
    - 37 drawings, undated (Folder 348)
    - 37 drawings, undated (Folder 349)
    - 37 drawings, undated (Folder 350)
  - 3:26 Britton Hadden Memorial - Yale Daily News (13 drawings), undated (Box 351)
  - 3:31 Chinese Language Department (215 Park St):, furniture (1 drawing), undated (Box 351)
  - 3:32 204 York Street, Property Map. Copy, 1928 October 22 (Folder 631)
  - 3:33 205-207 Park St.: heating units (1 drawing), undated (Box 351)
  - 3:43 Art and Architecture Building
    - Original section perspective (ink and zipatone on board) signed by Paul Rudolph, 1960 (Folder 660)
      Custodial History
      Given in the name and memory of Charles Gwathmey (MArch '62) to the Yale School of Architecture by Richard Nash Gould (YC '68; MArch '72), October 2007, on the occasion of the MArch 72's 35th reunion.
    - Library floor assignment (3 drawings), Paul Rudolph, 1961-1962, undated (Box 624)
    - Study Sheets (Box 696)
    - A1-A47, 1962 (Box 697)
    - 1962 (Box 698)
    - Revisions, 1975, 1981 (Box 699)
    - Revisions, 1986 (Box 700)
    - Extras (Box 701)
    - Extras (Box 702)
    - Extra Mechanicals (Box 703)
    - HVAC (Box 719)
    - Structural, 1964 (Box 720)
    - Structural, 1964 (Box 721)
    - Renovation Phase II B library floor plan. Basement, 1st floor, and 2nd floor, 1996 May 5 (Box 722)
    - Richard Meier, 2001 June-November (Box 742)
    - Studies for, 1996 July 8 (Box 742)
    - Polshek, 1996-1999 (Box 742)
    - Renovation - Polshek Proposal, 2000 (Box 748)
  - 3:53 87 Howe St
    - 1st-2nd Floor Plans (1), 1969 April 30 (Folder 636)
    - Basement Floor Plan and Section (1), 1969 June 17 (Folder 636)
  - 3:59 283-285 Dwight St.: kitchen plan (1 drawing), undated (Box 351)
  - 3:63 Fence Club (Psi Upsilon): originals (23 drawings), undated (Folder 355)
  - 4:3 Peabody Museum (Elm St): rendering (1 drawing), undated (Box 331)
  - 4:27 Delta Kappa Epsilon: originals (28 drawings), undated (Folder 357)
  - 4:28 Memorial Quadrangle
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 358)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 359)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 360)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 361)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 362)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 363)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 364)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 365)
    - Blueprints, undated (Folder 366)
    - Blueprints and some originals, undated (Folder 367)
    - Branford and Saybrook Colleges, elevation profiles (2 drawings), 1919 (Folder 599)
    - Branford and Saybrook colleges: schedules for finishes; J.G. Rogers (33 drawings), 1932-1933 (Folder 830)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Branford/ Saybrook) (Box 745)
    - Ren. 50% design development submission set 1 of 2 (Box 745)
    - Ren. Perry Dean Rogers, 1997 August 15 (Box 745)
    - Ren. GO.1, SU1.C1, L1.0-L11.0, D1.1, A1.0-.8, AB2.1-.13 (Box 745)
    - Ren. AS2.1-.13, AF2.1-.3, AB4.1-.5, AS4.1-.5, AB10.1-.2 (Box 745)
    - Ren. AS10.1-.3, RO-R61, SI-S30 (Box 745)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Branford/ Saybrook) (Box 745)
    - Ren. 90% construction documents I and II (Box 745)
    - Ren. Perry Dean Rogers, 1999 October 15 (Box 745)
    - Branford College (6 drawings), 1964 (Box 679)
    - Branford College- Saybrook College, 1932 (Box 679)
    - Berkeley College (BK), Branford College (BR), Saybrook College (SY), Timothy Dwight College (TD)
      - Program scope development (Box 778)
      - H.S. Newman, 1996 (Box 778)
      - New Residential Hall (Box 778)
      - New Residential Hall - H.S. Newman, 1997 June 20 (Box 778)
  - 4:29 Weir Hall (66 High St): blueprints, plans (6 drawings), undated (Folder 368)
  - 4:34 Dickinson and Wheelock Halls (Jonathan Edwards): prints and originals (37 drawings), undated (Folder 369)
  - 4:34 Dickinson and Wheelock Halls (Jonathan Edwards): prints and originals (37 drawings), undated (Folder 370)
  - 4:37 Yale University Art Gallery
    - Drawings and prints, undated (Box 371)
    - Drawings and prints, undated (Box 372)
    - Drawings and prints, undated (Box 373)
    - Drawings and prints, undated (Box 374)
    - Drawings and prints, undated (Box 375)
    - Drawings and prints, undated (Box 771)
    - Addition, 1951-1954 (Folder 640)
    - Addition, 1951-1954 (Folder 641)
    - Addition, 1951-1954 (Folder 642)
    - Remodeling, Paul Rudolph
      - Study #1(6 drawings), 1958 January 23 (Box 624)
      - Study #2 (6 drawings), 1958 January 23 (Box 624)
      - Longitudinal section of lecture room (3 drawings), undated (Box 624)
    - Drawing signed by L. Kahn, 1951 (Folder 660)
    - Floor plans (2), 1st floor, undated (Folder 660)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 742)
    - Status Report (Box 742)
    - Polshek, 2000 January 20 (Box 748)
    - Comprehensive Renovation, 2000 (Box 748)
    - Presentation Color, Polshek, 2000 (Box 748)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 749)
    - Phasing Scheme - color Polshek, 2000 (Box 749)
    - Kahn -original plans -gallery, 1963 (Box 748)
    - Selected sheets from Kahn/Orr construction document set: site plan, basement floor plan, first floor plan, north elevation (section d-d), west elevation, south elevation), 1952 (Box 748)
    - Selected sheets from Newman construction document set: site plan, basement floor plan, basement roof plan, basement reflected ceiling plan, sections, basement roof details, structural, 1977 June 15 (Box 748)
    - Comprehensive Renovation - Newman -original plans, 1973 (Box 748)
    - Art Gallery (Box 763)
    - A1-A16 (Box 764)
    - A50-99 (Box 765)
    - 100-End (Box 766)
    - Art Gallery, Memorial Quad (Box 767)
    - Early schemes (Box 768)
    - Details, undated (Folder 829)
    - Clock face detail, designed by Samuel Yellin, 1928 (Box 911)
  - 4: Library and High Streets, Manhole Detail Plan, 1931 October 26 (Folder 633)
  - 5:10 Hall of Graduate Studies (320 York St):
    - prints and originals (37 drawings), undated (Folder 376)
    - prints and originals (37 drawings), undated (Folder 377)
    - Site Map of Proposed Graduate Buildings on the NW corner of Tower Parkway and York Street. Annotated, 1930 (Folder 631)
    - Site Map of Proposed Graduate Buildings on the NW corner of Tower Parkway and York Street. Signed by James Gamble Rogers, 1930 January 17 (Folder 631)
    - Plot plan of the Yale Graduate School, 1932 February 2 (Folder 638)
  - 5:16, Morse and 5:17 Stiles Colleges
    - 12 drawings, undated (Box 351)
    - Buttery (2 drawings) (Folder 600)
  - 5: 15 Broadway, Elevation (1) and Floor Plan (1), 1949 December 31 (Folder 630)
  - 6:4 Central Power Plant
    - Elevations (1 drawing), undated (Box 351)
    - Map of existing and proposed heating and electric mains for the Central Heating and Lighting Plant, 1911 April 15 (Folder 648)
    - Blueprints (3), 1916-1919 (Folder 633)
  - 6:5 University Operations: alterations (3 drawings), undated (Box 351)
  - 6:6 56-58 Lake Place, 1st-3rd Floor Plans (3). Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
  - 6:7, 6:8 62-64 Lake Place, 1st-3rd Floor Plans (5). Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
  - 6:9 68 Lake Place
    - 1st-3rd Floor Plans (3). Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
    - 1st and 2nd Floor Plans. Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
  - 6:16 Payne Whitney Gymnasium (70 Tower Pkwy)
    - 24 drawings, undated (Folder 381)
    - 2 drawings, 1932 (Box 679)
    - Bound drawings, 1930-1931 (Box 783)
    - Rifle and Pistol Range (1) and Unidentified Plan (1), Tracings, 1940, undated (Folder 633)
  - 6:22 102 York Street: alterations (2 drawings), undated (Box 351)
  - 6: York Sq. Tunnel to Gymnasium, Plan, 1929 May 24 (Folder 631)
  - 6: 20 Ashumn St
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (194 drawings), 1917-1993 (Box 751)
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (194 drawings), 1917-1993 (Box 759)
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (194 drawings), 1917-1993 (Box 760)
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (194 drawings), 1917-1993 (Box 761)
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (194 drawings), 1917-1993 (Box 762)
  - 6: 26, 28, 30, 32, 50 Ashmun St
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (30 drawings), 1957-1985 (Box 752)
  - 6: 40-42 Lake Place, 1st-3rd Floor Plans (5). Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
  - 6: 46-48 Lake Place, 1st-3rd Floor Plans (5). Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
  - 6: 72-74 Lake Place, 1st-3rd Floor Plans (5). Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
  - 6: 78 Lake Place
    - Basement Plan, 1969 June 30 (Folder 634)
    - 1st Floor Plan, 1969 June 30 (Folder 634)
    - 2nd Floor Plan, 1969 June 30 (Folder 634)
    - 3rd Floor Plan, 1939 June 30 (Folder 634)
    - 1st-3rd Floor Plans. Sketches, undated (Folder 634)
  - 6: 96-98 Lake Place, Floor Plans (3), 1982 September 29 (Folder 630)
  - 7:4 Yale Gym Group-Amphitheater Unit, 1930 (Box 679)
  - 7:31 Sterling Memorial Library (120 High St)
    - Originals and prints; J.G. Rogers (Folder 383)
    - Originals and prints; J.G. Rogers (Folder 384)
    - Originals and prints; J.G. Rogers (Box 385)
    - Renditions of entrance to; James G. Rogers, architect, circa 1928 (Folder 572)
    - Floor Plan (1) and Air Conditioning Plan (1), 1928 August 22, undated (Folder 630)
    - Mezzanine addition, J. Russell Bailey, 1963 September 30 (Folder 580)
    - Mezzanine addition, J. Russell Bailey, 1963 September 30 (Folder 646)
    - Mezzanine addition, J. Russell Bailey, 1963 September 30 (Folder 647)
    - Sterling Memorial Library extension, 1968 (Folder 834)
    - Plans for sub-basement, basement, first through seventh floors, first and second floor mezzanines, and roof level (12 drawings), 1984 August 29 (Box 624)
    - Terminal installation, Paul Sargent, 1988 September 30 (Box 624)
    - Plans, sections, tables, and details (5 drawings) (Box 624)
    - Presentation panels of proposed Music Library by Cesar Pelli and Associates, circa 1988 (Box 666)
    - Phase I Renovations (Shepley, Bullfinch, Richardson, and Abbot, Architects), 1994
      - Floor plans (Box 672)
      - Floor plans (Box 673)
      - Floor plans (Box 674)
      - Floor plans (Box 676)
      - Floor plans (Box 688)
      - Floor plans (Box 689)
      - Preliminary design submission, 1994 October 17 (Box 672)
      - Preliminary design submission, 1994 October 17 (Box 673)
      - Preliminary design submission, 1994 October 17 (Box 674)
      - Preliminary design submission, 1994 October 17 (Box 676)
      - Preliminary design submission, 1994 October 17 (Box 688)
      - Preliminary design submission, 1994 October 17 (Box 689)
      - Presentation plans, 1994 September (Folder 737)
      - Floor plans, 1994 September 7 (Box 672)
      - Floor plans, 1994 September 7 (Box 673)
      - Floor plans, 1994 September 7 (Box 674)
      - Floor plans, 1994 September 7 (Box 676)
      - Floor plans, 1994 September 7 (Box 688)
      - Floor plans, 1994 September 7 (Box 689)
    - Phase I Renovations, 1995
      - Final check plot, 1995 March 29 (Box 659)
      - Final check plot, 1995 March 29 (Box 675)
      - Final check plot, 1995 March 29 (Box 677)
      - Final check plot, 1995 March 29 (Box 690)
      - Final check plot, 1995 March 29 (Box 691)
      - Final check plot, 1995 March 29 (Box 692)
      - 50% construction set, 1995 April 10 (Box 659)
      - 50% construction set, 1995 April 10 (Box 675)
      - 50% construction set, 1995 April 10 (Box 677)
      - 50% construction set, 1995 April 10 (Box 690)
      - 50% construction set, 1995 April 10 (Box 691)
      - 50% construction set, 1995 April 10 (Box 692)
      - 90% construction set, 1995 June 16 (Box 659)
      - 90% construction set, 1995 June 16 (Box 675)
      - 90% construction set, 1995 June 16 (Box 677)
      - 90% construction set, 1995 June 16 (Box 690)
      - 90% construction set, 1995 June 16 (Box 691)
      - 90% construction set, 1995 June 16 (Box 692)
      - Bid set and addendum, 1995 July (Box 659)
      - Bid set and addendum, 1995 July (Box 675)
      - Bid set and addendum, 1995 July (Box 677)
      - Bid set and addendum, 1995 July (Box 690)
      - Bid set and addendum, 1995 July (Box 691)
      - Bid set and addendum, 1995 July (Box 692)
    - Renovations, 1996-1997 (Box 693)
    - Renovations, 1995-1997 (Box 313)
    - Renovations, 1995-1997 (Box 694)
    - Library renovation, 7th floor lighting, 1995 April 21 (Box 694)
    - Librarian's Court Yard, 1997 April 22 (Box 694)
    - Design parameter interior matrix, 1993 October (Folder 732)
    - Map Collection: architect's conception, Undated (Box 722)
    - Periodicals reading room, 1997 June 27 (Box 725)
    - Periodicals Room, 1997 March 11-April 11 (Box 907)
    - Periodicals Room electrical plans, 1997 June 27 (Box 908)
    - Music Library
      - Presentation Plans, (Shepley, Bullfinch, Richardson, and Abbot, Architects), 1994 Sep, October (Folder 735)
      - Presentation Plans, (Shepley, Bullfinch, Richardson, and Abbot, Architects), 1994 Sep, October (Box 738)
      - Scheme 5, 1994 June 20 (Box 722)
      - Scheme 6, 1994 June 20 (Box 722)
      - Floor plan, 1994 November 20 (Box 722)
      - Schematic, 1995 January 27 (Box 722)
      - Architectural and structural plans -vol. I - II, Electrical as builts, Fire alarm electrical as builts, Mechanical drawings, 1996 December 9 (Box 726)
      - Architectural and structural plans -vol. I - II, Electrical as builts, Fire alarm electrical as builts, Mechanical drawings, 1996 December 9 (Box 727)
      - Architectural and structural plans -vol. I - II, Electrical as builts, Fire alarm electrical as builts, Mechanical drawings, 1996 December 9 (Box 728)
      - Architectural and structural plans -vol. I - II, Electrical as builts, Fire alarm electrical as builts, Mechanical drawings, 1996 December 9 (Box 729)
      - Architectural and structural plans -vol. I - II, Electrical as builts, Fire alarm electrical as builts, Mechanical drawings, 1996 December 9 (Box 730)
      - Architectural and structural plans -vol. I - II, Electrical as builts, Fire alarm electrical as builts, Mechanical drawings, 1996 December 9 (Box 731)
      - Floor plans, 1995 (Box 904)
      - Electrical "as-built", 1995, 1999 (Box 905)
      - Fire alarms "as-built", 1997-1999 (Box 906)
    - Renovations, 2003 (Box 714)
    - Renovations, 2003 (Box 715)
    - Renovations, 2003 (Box 716)
    - Renovations, 2003 (Box 717)
    - Renovations, 2003 (Box 718)
      - Computer files
        - 01. Emergency Repairs, 2004-a-009-0001; 1 (Box 718A)
          General note
          Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
        - 02. Assignment Plans, 2004-a-009-0002; 1 (Box 718A)
        - 03. Periodicals Reading Room, 2004-a-009-0003; 1 (Box 718A)
        - 04. Music Library, 2004-a-009-0004; 1 (Box 718A)
        - 05. Phase One Renovations, 2004-a-009-0005; 1 (Box 718A)
        - 06. Music Library, 2004-a-009-0006; 1; 357computer files (Box 718A)
        - 07. Phase One Renovations, 2004-a-009-0007; 1 (Box 718A)
        - 08. Periodicals Reading Room, 2004-a-009-0008; 1 (Box 718A)
    - Lighting plans (presentation), 1994 September (Folder 734)
    - Newspaper reading room (Sargent and Merriman), 1990 (Folder 733)
    - Newspaper reading room (Sargent and Merriman), 1990 (Box 738)
    - Renovation, 1991-1992 (Box 739)
    - Stack plans, revisions (architectural) (19 drawings), Undated (Box 740)
    - Various library projects, 1985-1990 (Box 736)
    - Window drawings for Phase I renovations, Circa 1996
      Drawings of windows detail the location of leading and brass. Each drawing includes a number where WD stands for window and the letter-number combination is a unique identifier assigned to each window. The amount of restoration needed and the date the window was removed for repair are also recorded.
      - WD S-1 (Box 863)
      - WD S-2 (Box 864)
      - WD S-3 (Box 865)
      - WD S-4 (Box 866)
      - WD S-5 (Box 867)
      - WD S-6 (Box 868)
      - WD S-7 (Box 869)
      - WD S-8 (Box 870)
      - WD S-9 (Box 871)
      - WD S-10 (Box 872)
      - WD S-11 (Box 873)
      - WD S-12 (Box 874)
      - WD S-13 (Box 875)
      - WD S-14 (Box 876)
      - WD S-15 (Box 877)
      - WD S-16 (Box 878)
      - WD S-17 (Box 879)
      - WD N-1 and N-2 (Box 880)
      - WD N-3 and N-4 (Box 881)
      - WD N-5 through N-10 (Box 882–883)
      - WD E-1, E-2 (Box 884)
      - Stacktower fourth floor, N,S, E elevation WD (Box 885–886)
      - Stacktower fifth floor WD S-17 through S-23, N-21 through N-24 (Box 887)
      - Stacktower fifth floor east elevation WD (Box 888–889)
      - Stacktower sixth floor WD E-1 through E-7 (Box 890)
      - Stacktower sixth floor elevation N, S WD (Box 891–892)
      - Stacktower sixth floor E elevation WD E-8 through E-13 (Box 893)
      - Stacktower seventh floor N,S elevation WD (Box 894–896)
      - Stacktower seventh floor WD E-1 through E-7 (Box 897)
      - Stacktower seventh floor WD E-8 through E-13 (Box 898)
      - Windows MA-1 through MA-6, MA-10 through MA 20 (Box 899)
    - SML construction bid set, 1995 July 25 (Box 900)
    - SML Phase I Renovation "as-built" Ducci Electrical Contractor, 1995, 1999 (Box 901–902)
    - Electrical and fire alarms "as-built" Ducci Electrical Contractor, 1995-1999 (Box 903)
  - 7:36 Trumbull College (241 Elm St)
    - 113 Drawings, undated (Folder 387–394)
    - 4 drawings, 1932 (Box 679)
  - 8:16 Sterling Law Buildings (127 Wall St)
    - 12 drawings, undated (Box 395)
    - AC Distribution Plan (2), 1 Blueprint and 1 Tracing, 1958 March 12 (Folder 633)
    - Yale Law Library, Floor Plan, 1952 October 22 (Folder 633)
    - Yale Law Library Extension, Floor Plans (3), undated (Folder 633)
  - 9:19 Lampson Lyseum: seating plan (1 drawing), undated (Folder 396)
  - 9:23 Noah Porter Gateway (3 drawings), undated (Folder 397)
  - 9:24 Albert Sprague Memorial Hall, undated (Folder 398)
  - 9:33 William L. Harkness Hall (100 Wall St)
    - 4 drawings, undated (Folder 399)
    - Architectural Details, 1926-1927 (Box 800, Box 800B–800C)
    - 3 drawings, undated (Folder 834)
    - Detail Plans (2), 1951 March - April (Folder 633)
  - 9:34 Calhoun College (189 Elm St)
    - 3 drawings, undated (Box 395)
    - Drawings, 1931 (Box 679)
      Includes four photographic print reproductions.
  - 9:35 Berkeley College (205 Elm St)
    - 6 drawings, undated (Box 395)
    - 3 drawings, 1933 (Box 679)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Count of Original Construction Documents, 1994 (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. James Gamble Rogers (Box 746–747)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Progress Set 1996 I and II (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Kieran Timberlake and Harris (Box 746–747)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Progress Set I and II, 1996 (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Kieran Timberlake and Harris (Box 746–747)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Preliminary Design I and II (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Kieran Timberlake and Harris, 1996 November 4 (Box 746–747)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. 90% Contract Documents I and II (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Kieran Timberlake and Harris, 1997 July 31 (Box 746–747)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. 100% Design Development (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Kieran Timberlake and Harris, 1997 January 13 (Box 746–747)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Berkeley) (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Flexible Housing Options - user handbook (Box 746–747)
    - Ren. Kieran Timberlake and Harris, 1999 (Box 746–747)
  - 9:36 Cross Campus Library (120 High St)
    - 1 drawing, undated (Box 395)
    - Edward Larabee Barnes, 1971 (Box 574)
    - Cross Campus Library: phase I "as built" drawings, Edward Larrabee Barnes, architect, 1964 August 1
      - [Wall plan?], 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Site plan, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Upper level plan, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Lower level plan, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - [Tunnel level?], 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Lower level, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Sections looking east and north, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Sections: east exit court, tunnel to Berkeley, Sterling tunnel, book lift, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Sections, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Plan of mullion location, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Stairs, court, and plaza, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Entrance court doors, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Entrance court window wall, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Stairs and elevators, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Interior elevations, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Toilet rooms, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Circulation and reserve desks and card catalog, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
      - Doors, 1964 August 1 (Box 626)
    - Wheelchair access project (33 drawings), 1971 (Box 601)
    - Electronic classroom renovation floor plans, notes, and specifications, 1999 January 4 (Box 723)
  - 9:37 Blount Avenue (1 drawing), undated (Folder 403)
  - 10:1 Kingsley Trust Association (Scroll and Key) building (490 College St), 1898-1959 (Folder 667–671)
  - 10:13 Bicentennial Buildings
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Folder 404)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Folder 405)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Folder 406)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Folder 407)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Folder 408)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Box 409)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Box 410)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Folder 411)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Box 412)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Box 413)
    - Blueprints on linen (208 drawings), undated (Box 414)
    - Memorial Building (Grove and College): Plan of ceiling, 1902 (Folder 836)
  - 10:13 Woolsey Hall
    - Miscellaneous Architectural Details, 1911-1913, 1929 (Box 800, Box 800A)
  - 10:18 Woodbridge Hall (105 Wall St)
    - 16 drawings, undated (Folder 416–419)
    - Front elevation, basement, and 1st floor plans (3 drawings), 1900 (Folder 603)
    - Renovations (3 drawings), 1970 (Folder 836)
  - 10:23 117 Wall St. (1 drawing), undated (Box 409)
  - 10:24 Beinecke Library (9 drawings), undated (Box 409)
  - 10:25 Hewitt Quadrangle (1 drawing), undated (Folder 422)
  - 10: Book and Snake, Kitchen Plan, 1961 February 28 (Folder 630)
  - 11:3 Hendrie Hall (165 Elm St) (2 drawings), undated (Box 423)
  - 11:9 143 Elm St. (2 drawings), undated (Box 423)
  - 11:10 66 Wall St. (4 drawings), undated (Folder 425)
  - 11:11 Faculty Club (8 drawings), undated (Folder 426)
  - 11:17 435 College St. (2 drawings), undated (Box 423)